<resources>
    <string name="app_name">My Application</string>
    <string name="skills">
    COMPUTER SKILLS\n
 MySQL\n
 DBMS\n
 Python\n
 C++ Language\n
 RDBMS\n
 Machine Learning\n
 HTML\n
 CSS\n
 Javascript\n
 OOPs\n
 MS Office\n
 Advanced MS Excel\n
 Tableau\n
</string>

 <string name="education">
  1.Birla Institute of Technology, Mesra , India (07/2018- 05-2018)-\n
Integrated Master of Science in Mathematics and Computing GPA-7.76\n
2.Delhi Public School, Bokaro Steel City, India (07/2016-03/2018)\n
Class 12, CBSE Percentage in Science-82.2%\n
3.Delhi Public School, Bokaro Steel city, India (04/2015-03/2016)\n
Class 10, CBSE CGPA-10\n
 </string>

 <string name="workexperience">
  1. Tata Steel: Summer Internship-Project on House Price Prediction (01/2023-04/2023)\n


  2. College Project, BIT Mesra: Probabilistic Analysis of some Ragas of Thaat Kafi (01/2023-05/2023)\n
 Evaluated conditional probability to identify the Ragas By Transition Probability Matrix and unconditional probability to plot\n
 Andrews curves using Python to judge the similarity amongst the curves.\n


  3. 4th Indian Workshop on Applied Deep Learning (06/2023-06/2023)\n
  workshop included architecture that demonstrated the potential to solve a broad range of computer vision and NLP\n
 problems, achieving optimization over high dimensional parametric space.\n


  4. Feynn Labs :Machine Learning Internship- (06/2023-08/2023)AI Product/Service Prototype Ideation-During this period,I have come up with a product Idea of Heart Attack Prediction App\n
 using Machine Learning and gave a business modeling diagram.\n


  5. Zummit Infolabs :Deep Learning Internship (08/2023-12/2023)\n
   make projects on RNN, LSTM, CNN, image recognition, Facial Features detection, MNIST Handwritten digits using CNN\n
 make projects on AlexNet- image classification of Cifar dataset having airplanes, dogs, ship, birds etc using AlexNet, Object\n
 detection using YOLO, Program to classify email spam or not\n
 </string>

 <string name="achievements">
 1.Recieved first position in Insignia-Poster Making Competition at BIT Mesra.\n
 2.Sangeet Vishaarad in Hindustani classical Music.\n
 3.4 Stars(silver) in Python- Hackerank.\n
 4.4 Stars(silver) in SQL -Hackerank.\n
 5.My College Project/Thesis "Probabilistic Analysis of Some Ragas of Thata Kafi" is Published
as a book.\n
 </string>
</resources>